14.5
Hi Tim. How was your holiday?
Chào Tim. Kỳ nghỉ của bạn thế nào?
Oh, it was fantastic, thanks.
Ồ, tuyệt vời lắm, cảm ơn.
The hotel was great.
Khách sạn rất tuyệt.
There was a big swimming pool
Có một hồ bơi lớn
and there was a table tennis table too.
và cũng có một bàn bóng bàn nữa.
Oh, that was lucky. You like table tennis.
Ồ, may mắn thật. Bạn thích bóng bàn mà.
Was there a computer room?
Có phòng máy tính không?
No, there wasn't.
Không, không có.
But our room was nice.
Nhưng phòng của chúng tôi rất đẹp.
There was a big TV in it.
Có một chiếc ti vi lớn trong phòng.
Nice. And was there a good beach?
Tuyệt. Và có bãi biển đẹp không?
Well, no, there wasn't.
À, không, không có.
We weren't near the sea.
Chúng tôi không ở gần biển.
There were mountains.
Có những ngọn núi.
It was a very small place
Đó là một nơi rất nhỏ
and there weren't any shops.
và không có cửa hàng nào.
Wow! It was a small place.
Ồ! Đó là một nơi nhỏ.
Yes. There were some cafes
Vâng. Có vài quán cà phê
and there was a restaurant
và có một nhà hàng
and oh yes, there was a small museum.
và ồ vâng, có một bảo tàng nhỏ.
But that's it.
Nhưng chỉ có vậy thôi.
It was a bit boring really.
Thật ra hơi chán.